Guide to the Historical Planning publications collection, 1888-2002.
Historical Planning publications collection
- Series VIII. Law
  - Law-Foreign-Netherlands (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - A New Legal Arrangement for Physical Planning and Housing in the Netherlands, September 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Ministry of Housing and Building, The Hague
    - Housing and Planning Legislation in the Netherlands, January 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      J. Bommer, Ministry of Housing and Building, The Hague
    - Brief Summary of the Physical Planning Act, July 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Series IX. Local Government
  - Local Government-General (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Governmental Units Overlying City Areas, October 1, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Department of Commerce, Bureau of the Census
    - Structure of Governments in Metropolitan Areas, November 1, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Illinois Legislative Council
    - An Advisory Committee Report on Local Government, June 1, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      U.S. Commission on Intergovernmental Relations
    - Reports Adopted By National Conference on Metropolitan Problems, August 1, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Local Government-General (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Recommendations and Major Statements of the Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, August 1, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Federal Government and Metropolitan Areas, October 22, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      U.S. Bureau of the Budget
    - Adaptacion Gubernamental a las Necesidades Metropolitanas (Adapting Government to Metropolitan Needs), January 1, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      El Instituto Nacional de Vivienda y Urbanismo, San Jose, Costa Rica
    - The Charter Problem of Metropolitan Cities, January 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Citizens Union
    - Ideas for a Better City (Tennessee), December 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Municipal Technical Advisory Service, University of Tennessee and Tennessee Municipal League
    - Ideas for a Better City (Tennessee), January 1, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Local Government-General (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Selected Areas of Intergovernmental Cooperation, January 1, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Pennsylvania Department of Interior Affairs
    - The American County Platform, July 31, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      National Association of Counties
    - Federal-State-Local Relations, June 23, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      U.S. Congressional Record, 89th Congress, 2nd Session, v112, no. 103
    - The Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, May 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Modernizing Local Government, January 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Councils of Governments - An Approach to Regional Problems, November 1, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Division of Planning, Indiana Dept. of Commerce
  - Local Government-U.S.- Alaska (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Local Governmental Office Space Needs, August 30, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Site Location Study, Local Government Office Space, May 1, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Local Government-U.S.- California (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Regional Home Rule and Government of the San Francisco Bay Area, February 22, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Association of Bay Area Governments
    - Association of Bay Area Governments Fact Sheet, May 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      County of Santa Clara Planning Department
    - Government Reorganization for Metropolitan Sacramento, June 1, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Metropolitan Government Committee
    - Regional Home Rule Proposal, February 7, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Local Government-U.S.- Colorado (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - City Managers and Councils - Charter Provisions in Colorado Home-Rule Cities, January 1, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      John C. Buechner, Bureau of Governmental Research and Service, University of Colorado, Boulder
    - Local Government in Colorado, January 1, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Governor's Local Affairs Study Commission
  - Local Government-U.S.- Illinois (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Illinois Municipal Problems, January 1, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Cities and Villages Municipal Problems Commission
    - Illinois Municipal Problems, January 1, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - The Government of the City of Chicago. A Guide to Its Structure and Function with a Directory of Officers, November 1, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Illinois Municipal Problems, January 1, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Local Government-U.S.- Kansas (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Extension of Municipal Services to Fringe Areas, March 31, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Eugene H. Denton, Governmental Research Center, Univ. of Kansas
  - Local Government-U.S.- Michigan (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Local Government in Genesee County, October 13, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Cost and Effect of Changing From Village to City, November 1, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Michigan Municipal League
    - How the Huron-Clinton Metropolitan Authority Responds to Its Public, January 1, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
      Jerry C. Bosworth, Institute of Public Administration
  - Local Government-U.S.- Missouri (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Special Districts of Platte County, Missouri, Part I., April 1, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Governmental Research Bureau
  - Local Government-U.S.- New York (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Rural Government in New York, September 1, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      M.P. Catherwood, T.N. Hurd, C.A. Bratton, Cornell University
    - Local Government in Tompkins County, New York, August 1, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      T. N. Hurd, Cornell University Agricultural Experiment Station
    - Local Government in Cattaraugus County, New York, June 1, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      M.P. Catherwood and T.N. Hurd, Cornell University
    - Your City Government. Schenectady, N.Y. 1939, January 1, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Local Government-U.S.- New York (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Nassau County Government, January 1, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      J. Russell Sprague, County Governor
    - Your City Government. Schenectady, N.Y. 1940, January 1, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Your City Government. Schenectady, N.Y. 1941, January 1, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Rochester Since 'Twenty-Eight. A Diagrammatic Study, January 1, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Rochester Bureau of Municipal Research
    - Know Your City Government, Ithaca, New York., September 1, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      League of Women Voters of Tompkins County, 2 copies
    - Considerations for Revising the City Charter, May 8, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Syracuse Charter Revision Committee
    - A New Charter for the City of New York, January 16, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 16)
      New York State Commission on Governmental Operations of the City of New York
  - Local Government-U.S.- Ohio (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Research Program for Cleveland Metropolitan Services Commission, October 1, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Metro Cleveland Metropolitan Government. A Preliminary Statement..., September 6, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Cleveland Metropolitan Services Commission
    - County Government in Ohio, November 1, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Selected Metropolitan Area Problems. Section 1. The Municipal Income Tax; Section 2. Mass Transportation in Ohio; Section 3. Alternative Forms of County Government, February 1, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Ohio Legislative Service Commission
    - A Continuing Research Program for Metropolitan Cleveland, October 15, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Cleveland Bureau of Governmental Research, Inc.
  - Local Government-U.S.- Pennsylvania (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Demand for Action, September 1, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Thomas Evans
  - Local Government-U.S.- Rhode Island (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Directory of Local Government Officials In Rhode Island, January 1, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Directory of Local Government Officials In Rhode Island, February 1, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Directory of State Associations of Local Governmental Officials, June 1, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Local Government-U.S.- Tennessee (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Nashville and Davidson County, Tennessee Consider Metropolitan Government (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Irving Hand, Nashville City and Davidson County Planning Commissions, post 1954
    - A Brief Summary of the Proposed Metropolitan Charter for Knox County and Knoxville, April 9, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Metropolitan Government Charter Commission
    - How to Become A City. Procedures Under Each of Tennessee's Uniform Charters., March 1, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Local Government-U.S.- Virginia (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Governing the Virginia Metropolitan Areas - An Assessment, May 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Metropolitan Virginia 1967 - A Brief Assessment, May 1, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Local Government-U.S.- Wisconsin (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Report of the Metropolitan Development Committee (City of Madison, WI), April 1, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Local Government-Foreign- Canada (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - An Address to the Inaugural Meeting of the Council of the Municipality of Metropolitan Toronto, January 11, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Frederick G. Gardiner, Q.C., Chairman of the Council
    - Metropolitan Government and Regional Planning. Problem and Practice and Application to Montreal, May 1, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Montreal Board of Trade
    - Metropolitan Area Government - The Toronto Experience, January 1, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      John G. Grumm
  - Local Government-Foreign- Great Britain (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - The Herbert Report and the Values of Local Government, June 1, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      Peter Self, Extract from Political Studies, Vol. 10, No. 2
- Series X. Metropolitan Areas
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - General, 1955-1961 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Arkansas, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - California, 1958-1981 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Georgina, 1956-1962 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Kentucky - Lexington, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Minnesota, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - New York, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - North Carolina, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Ohio, 1947-1961 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Puerto Rico, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Tennessee, 1955-1966 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Areas - U.S. - Washington, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Areas - Foreign - Canada - Toronto, 1954-1967 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Areas - Foreign - Canada - Toronto (Oversized), 1965 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Areas - Foreign - Canada - Toronto (Oversized), 1966 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Areas - Foreign - Canada - Toronto (Oversized), 1968 (Box 69)
  - Metropolitan Areas - Foreign - Canada - Winnipeg (1), 1953-1974 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Areas - Foreign - Canada - Winnipeg (2), 1954-1961 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Series XI. Mobile Homes and Parks
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - General (1), 1939-1956 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - General (2), 1958-1960 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - General (3), 1961-1969 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - General (4) (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - California, 1942-1961 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - Kansas, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - Michigan, 1936-1939 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - Nevada, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - New Hampshire, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - New York, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - Ohio, 1958-1959 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Mobile Homes and Parks - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Series XII. Nations
  - Nations - Argentina, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Nations - Australia, 1943 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Nations - Cameroon, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Nations - Canada, 1943-1949 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Nations - Columbia, 1954-1956 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Nations - Finland (1), 1943-1949 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Nations - Finland (2), 1963 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Nations - Great Britain (1), 1935-1943 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Nations - Great Britain (2) (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Nations - India, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Nations - Iraq, Circa 1956 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Nations - Israel (1), 1948-1958 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Nations - Israel (2), 1959-1964 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Nations - Japan, 1952-1954 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Nations - Jordan, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Nations - Latin America (1), 1950-1958 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Nations - Latin America (2), 1953-1958 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Nations - Mexico, 1959 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Nations - Netherlands, 1953-1967 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Nations - New Zealand, 1934-1940 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Nations - Nicaragua, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Nations - Panama (Oversized), 1956 (Box 69)
  - Nations - Pakistan, 1958-1961 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Nations - Poland, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Nations - Puerto Rico (1), 1941-1958 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Nations - Puerto Rico (2), 1943-1956 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Nations - Russia (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Nations - Spain, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Nations - Sweden, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Nations - United States, 1941-1962 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - Dept. of the Interior, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - HUD, 1965-1968 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - HUD - Addresses, 1966-1969 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - HUD - Addresses (Romney), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - HUD - Addresses (Weaver), 1966-1968 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - National Housing Agency, 1942-1943 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - National Planning Board, 1933 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - Natural Resources Committee, 1935-1936 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - Natural Resources Planning Board, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - Resettlement Administration, 1935 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Nations - U.S. - Agencies - WPA, 1936-1939 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Nations - Venezuela, 1954-1958 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Nations - West Indies (Oversized), 1958 (Box 69)
- Series XIII. Natural Resources
  - Natural Resources - General (1), 1942-1960 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Natural Resources - General (2), 1961-1968 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - Arizona, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - California, 1958 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - Connecticut, 1961 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - Illinois, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - Minnesota, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - New York, 1932-1950 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - North Carolina, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - North Dakota, circa 1934 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Natural Resources - U.S. - South Carolina, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Series XIV. Neighborhoods
  - Neighborhoods - General, 1941-1966 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Neighborhoods - California, 1960-1964 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Neighborhoods - Colorado, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Neighborhoods - Illinois, 1959-1967 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Neighborhoods - Michigan, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Neighborhoods - New York, 1955-1969 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Neighborhoods - Pennsylvania, 1932 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Neighborhoods - Rhode Island, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Neighborhoods - Tennessee, 1958-1959 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Neighborhoods - Foreign - Canada, 1947 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Neighborhoods - Foreign - Japan, 1967 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - General (1), 1941-1959 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - General (2), 1960-1968 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - California, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Illinois (1), 1951-1953 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Illinois (2), 1958-1962 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Illinois (3), 1956 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Massachusetts, 1950-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Michigan, 1950-1958 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - New York (1), 1943 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - New York (2), 1948-1960 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - North Carolina (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Ohio (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Pennsylvania, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Neighborhoods - Conservation - Virginia, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Series XV. New Towns
  - New Towns - General, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - New Towns - U.S. - California - Foster City, 1967-1972 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - New Towns - U.S. - Illinois, 1948-1950 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - New Towns - U.S. - Maryland, 1936-1971 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - New Towns - U.S. - New Jersey, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - New Towns - U.S. - New York State, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - New Towns - U.S. - Ohio (1), 1936-1937 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - New Towns - U.S. - Ohio (2), 1949 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - New Towns - U.S. - Virginia, 1963-1967 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - New Towns - U.S. - Wisconsin, 1958-1959 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - New Towns - Foreign, 1959-1967 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - New Towns - Australia - Elizabeth, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - General, 1922-1967 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Basildon, 1964-1968 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Bracknell, 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Bracknell (Oversized), 1957 (Box 69)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Corby, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Crawley, 1950-1969 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Cumbernauld, 1966-1968 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Cwmbran, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - East Kilbride, 1967-1968 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Glenrothes, 1948-1968 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Harlow, 1951-1966 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Hatfield, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Hemel Hampstead, 1968 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Letchworth, 1919 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Livingston, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Runcorn, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Skeimersdale, 1963-1968 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Stevenage, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Washington, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Welwyn, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Great Britain - Welwyn (Oversized), 1957 (Box 69)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Israel (Oversized), 1958 (Box 69)
  - New Towns - Foreign - Pakistan, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Series XVI. Organizations
  - Organizations - A.C.T.I.O.N., 1967 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Organizations - American City Planning Institute, 1936 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Organizations - American Institute Of Planners (1), 1949-1957 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Organizations - American Institute Of Planners (2), 1965-1968 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Organizations - American Society Of Planning Officials (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Organizations - Association For Planning And Regional Reconstruction, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Organizations - California University Real Estate Research, 1966-1968 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Organizations - Citizens' Housing And Planning Council, 1960-1961 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Organizations - Cleveland Development Foundation, 1954-1959 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Organizations - Columbia University Bureau Of Applied Social Research, 1962-1965 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Organizations - Columbia University Institute For Urban Life and Land Use Studies (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Organizations - Columbia University School Of Architecture - Institute Of Urban Environment, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Organizations - Community Planning Association of Canada, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Organizations - Connecticut Federation Of Planning And Zoning Agencies, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Organizations - Delaware Valley Council (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Organizations - Detroit Metropolitan Area Regional Planning Commission, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Organizations - Ford Foundation, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Organizations - Housing And Home Financy Agency, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Organizations - Institute Of Public Administration, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Organizations - Inter-American Housing And Planning Center, 1953-1958 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Organizations - Inter-American Housing Research And Training Center, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Organizations - International Federation For Housing And Town Planning, 1958-1967 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Organizations - International Federation For Town And County Planning And Garden Cities (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Organizations - Joint Center For Urban Studies, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Organizations - Louiville University Urban Studies Center, 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Organizations - Michigan Society Of Planning Officials (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Organizations - Missouri University Center Of Community And Metropolitan Studies, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Organizations - National Association Of Home Builders, 1959-1961 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Organizations - National Association Of Housing And Redevelopment Officials, 1955-1968 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Organizations - National Association Of Real Estate Boards, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Organizations - National Commission On Urban Problems, 1967-1968 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Organizations - National Housing Conference, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Organizations - N.Y.C. Center For New York City Affairs Of The New School, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Organizations - N.Y.C. Twenty-Third Street Association, 1961 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Organizations - North Carolina University Center For Urban And Regional Studies, 1958-1967 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Organizations - Ohio - Dayton and Montgomery County Area Councils Service (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Organizations - Ohio Planning Conference, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - Organizations - Regional Plan Association, 1956-1961 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - Organizations - Regional Science Association, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - Organizations - United Nations, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - Organizations - United Nations (Oversized), 1946 (Box 61)
  - Organizations - Urban Land Institute, 1944 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - Organizations - Western Michigan University Institute of Public Affairs, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 52)
- Series XVII. Parking
  - Parking - General (1), 1936-1944 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Parking - General (2), 1946 (Box 47, Folder 54)
  - Parking - General (3), 1947-1948 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Parking - General (4), 1948 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Parking - General (5), 1949 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Parking - General (6), 1950-1952 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Parking - General (7), 1953-1956 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Parking - General (8), 1957-1964 (Box 48, Folder 6)